<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>[Super Duper Fantastic]</title>
    <description>A lifestyle/personal blog exploring food, travel and unique experiences and adventures in San Francisco and around the world.</description>
    <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 22:37:48 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 22:37:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bali at Sunset</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the abrupt return to real life and busy season, I haven’t quite processed all that I learned while in Bali. In between work and life things (and a little bit of travel too), I’m reliving some of the memories through what I’ve captured on my phone. In particular, the beauty of Bali at sunset. It’s pretty unforgettable.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1543/25180770930_c613415e2f_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bali at Sunset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m thinking about the projects that I want to work on to showcase the lessons learned from the ten days with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.instituteofcode.com/&quot; title=&quot;Institute of Code&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Institute of Code&lt;/a&gt;. We worked hard and played hard. We made the most of our time spent together, taking in coding lessons, a new place, and those crazy beautiful skies at sunset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1643/24850047213_0a1ed1b078_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bali at Sunset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my portfolio sites is finished, but it’s not quite ready to be revealed. Since I didn’t end up finding a company sponsor for my time with the program, I worked on a side project of Ryan’s. He is developing an app, and it’s still in progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1601/25108845989_69a40c4f0a_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bali at Sunset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve spent a few late nights tackling coding problems. This is only just the beginning. There are many more late nights to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m trying to recreate this blog in Jekyll. I’ve got the HTML and CSS part down, thanks to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.instituteofcode.com/&quot; title=&quot;Institute of Code&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Institute of Code&lt;/a&gt;. It’s getting everything else that I took for granted in WordPress, like slugs, tags and categories, to work. No worries - I figured those out eventually. That’s part of the learning process and pulling up the researching skills we learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1534/25476678825_e55c852596_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bali at Sunset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A friend of mine is currently in Bali for the course. He’s not only learning new technical skills, but undergoing a personal transformation, and it is so fulfilling to witness. I’ve been reliving Bali vicariously through his updates over social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1662/25476455055_2b10606a07_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bali at Sunset&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I look at what I was able to accomplish in only ten days, I’m surprised it all happened in a flash. I am grateful that such an opportunity exists and that I was able to participate.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 10:09:58 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/bali-at-sunset/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/bali-at-sunset/</guid>
        
        <category>Institute of Code</category>
        
        
        <category>Bali</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello a2 Milk - Goodbye Post-Dairy Digestive Discomfort!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This post was sponsored by a2 Milk ® as part of an Influencer Activation for Influence Central. I received complimentary products to facilitate my review.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1572/24873883514_830ea69c85_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a2 milk&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello! I am back from Bali and have hit the ground running. Busy season is busy at work, and all the while, I am trying hard to keep the jet lag from knocking me out. It’s a bit rough, but I’ve kept myself busy in the evenings after work. Once I’m ready to hit the bed, I’ve got the unnatural and natural sleep supplements handy, in case I can’t make it through the normal night time hours. Sleeping pills, melatonin, warm milk!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1578/24873685424_17e86b63a9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a2 Milk&quot; class=&quot;left&quot; /&gt; Speaking of milk, I am now a part of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://a2milk.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a2 Milk® Ambassador Program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growing up, I drank a lot of milk. As the milk habit waned, I started worrying that I would develop an intolerance to lactose as seemed to be the case among many Asians. I didn’t want to suffer through the discomforts that others seemed to go through when having an ice cream cone, a cheese plate, mac ‘n cheese, or cream in their coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, cheese and ice cream are not problems for me. It is usually the coffee, rather than the cream, that gets my tummy going, but there’s no denying that the relationship I have with milk as an adult is much different from when I was a child. Too much milk can lead to the grumbles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As it turns out, 1 in 4 Americans experiences discomfort after drinking milk. Of those cases, however, very few are actually due to lactose intolerance. Instead, it’s a sensitivity to the A1 protein found in most cow’s milk. If you haven’t been officially diagnosed with an intolerance to lactose, there is hope for you yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter &lt;a href=&quot;https://a2milk.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a2 Milk®&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the day, cows only had A2 proteins in their milk. As the cows were brought to America and adapted to local climate and conditions, many of the herds developed an A1 protein as well. The A1 protein is known to be responsible for post-dairy digestive discomfort that people often mistakenly associate with lactose intolerance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1545/25136315839_587cc20656_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a2 milk&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a recent addition to the a2 Milk® Ambassador Program, I’ve been reading up on what makes a2 Milk® different from regular milk and also other milk alternatives. So neat to see that there’s a natural way to do this! They’ve partnered up with dairy farmers in upstate New York and the Midwest to raise heirloom a2 cows that naturally produce milk free from the A1 protein. How crazy is that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d love to see them expand and raise these cows in California some day. For now, I’ll find a2 Milk ® at select Whole Foods and Safeways. Check the &lt;a href=&quot;https://a2milk.com/find/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;store finder for A1-free milk near you&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 18:35:58 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/a2-milk-goodbye-post-dairy-digestive-discomfort/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/a2-milk-goodbye-post-dairy-digestive-discomfort/</guid>
        
        <category>A2Milk</category>
        
        
        <category>Partners</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mexico City in 9 Days (Part IV)</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1445/23612030674_0ff2038a27_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-six-in-mexico-city---bosque-de-chapultepec--la-ciudadela--pujol&quot;&gt;DAY Six in Mexico City - Bosque de Chapultepec / La Ciudadela / Pujol&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started our day with green smoothies with our Airbnb hosts. Taking their advice and opting out of possibly encountering Friday traffic, we rode Ecobicis to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/pages/IVOIRE-Reatauranteur-Polanco/133780070123919&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ivoire&lt;/a&gt;, a restaurant recommended by our host. After breakfast, we made our way over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sedema.df.gob.mx/bosquedechapultepec&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bosque de Chapultepec&lt;/a&gt;, walked up to and strolled through &lt;a href=&quot;http://castillodechapultepec.inah.gob.mx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Castillo de Chapultepec&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1530/24433980813_416d728444_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Chapultepec&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The grounds and city below&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, we stopped in over at &lt;a href=&quot;http://museotamayo.org/restaurante&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Tamayo&lt;/a&gt; for drinks. Ryan’s request for &lt;em&gt;bebidas&lt;/em&gt; (“drinks”) was mistaken by the hostess as one for &lt;em&gt;pepitas&lt;/em&gt; (“pumpkin seeds”). Our Spanish is &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; bad - minor miscommunication there! After drinks at the museum cafe, we rode Ecobicis to &lt;a href=&quot;http://laciudadela.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;La Ciudadela&lt;/a&gt; where we wandered around the stalls to check out the crafts. We aren’t big on souvenirs, so we didn’t pick anything up at the market, but that’s the place to go if you are!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5791/23160149480_36c1fe0365_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Museo Tamayo&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Drinks at Restaurante Tamayo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before heading to dinner at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pujol.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pujol&lt;/a&gt;, one of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theworlds50best.com/list/1-50-winners/Pujol&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The World’s 50 Best Restaurants&lt;/a&gt;, we went home for a quick refresh. While it’s a prix fixe menu at Pujol, you do have to choose between a few items in several categories. Ryan and I split up our choices, so we could get a taste of as many items as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1525/24132390672_c3f7220af0_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Pujol&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Our fancy meal at Pujol&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we had said “Yes” to your Airbnb’s host’s invitation to see Lo Fang at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/tabernalucerna34/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Luciferina&lt;/a&gt; after dinner, we put our full and happy bellies in an Uber to the venue. The show was more expensive than many things we’d paid for in Mexico City, so that was a bit of a surprise. The show was on a rooftop, so we spent the evening dodging cigarette smoke. After the show, we grabbed tacos with our Airbnb hosts at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.taqueriaselfarolito.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;El Farolito in Polanco&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-seven-in-mexico-city---xochimilco--museo-dolores-olmedo--unam--muac&quot;&gt;Day Seven in Mexico City - Xochimilco / Museo Dolores Olmedo / UNAM &amp;amp; MUAC&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got up bright and early and took an Uber to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.museodoloresolmedo.org.mx&quot; title=&quot;Museo Dolores Olmedo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Dolores Olmedo&lt;/a&gt; in Xochimilco. It’s one of the longer Uber rides we took during our stay, but it was still under $12. Like the other museums, we bought a photography pass for each person taking photos. The exhibits of Diego Rivera and Frida Kahlo’s work were the main draw to the museum. An added bonus were the lovely grounds of the estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1703/24765220720_a49ab03196_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Dolores Olmedo&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Dolores Olmedo Museum&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we were done at the museum, we took an Uber to check out the canals of Xochimilco. We accidentally got talked onto a boat because of our very broken Spanish, but then we managed to finally get off the boat and walk away. If it weren’t just the two of us and our first time in the area, we probably would have gone for a ride. Once one commits to taking a boat, you’re on it for a few hours. We did find out that there’s some leeway in the price because they offered us one last price for the ride before we walked away. Instead, we walked around and took some photos before heading out of the area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1720/24765543260_65a72ee769_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Xochimilco&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Xochimilco&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we’d spent some time in Xochimilco, we took an Uber to the Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México (“UNAM”) for dinner and to check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://muac.unam.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Universitario Arte Contemporaneo&lt;/a&gt; (“MUAC”). The interactive exhibits at MUAC were another part of the trip that was unexpected, but fondly remembered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1576/23945027100_b1ef70da34_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - MUAC&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;h3 id=&quot;mexico-city---real-talk&quot;&gt;Mexico City - Real Talk&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://museotamayo.org/restaurante&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Tamayo&lt;/a&gt; for contemporary and modern art. We didn’t get a chance to this time, but we definitely will if we’re in Mexico City again.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Eat at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pujol.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pujol&lt;/a&gt;. For being one of the top restaurants, I was surprised to make a reservation without too much trouble. Get there right on time because they won’t let you in early. They’ll send you to their sister restaurant/cafe next door.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;If you’re a fan of Diego Rivera and Frida Kahlo’s work, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.museodoloresolmedo.org.mx&quot; title=&quot;Museo Dolores Olmedo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Dolores Olmedo&lt;/a&gt; is worth the trek to Xochimilco. In addition to the regular exhibits, there are some special exhibits that come through as well. While we were visiting, the exhibits were Dia de los Muertos themed.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;While we didn’t hop on a boat (“&lt;em&gt;trajinera&lt;/em&gt;”) ride, we wouldn’t hesitate to if we were in a larger group and if we had preparations for a picnic. That way, the cost of the boat is divided among more people, and we aren’t buying food and drinks on the spot.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://muac.unam.mx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MUAC&lt;/a&gt; for some interactive exhibits and an inexpensive meal at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/NubeSiete&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nube Siete&lt;/a&gt;. Enjoy a beverage if there’s a wait for your table.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:08:32 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/mexico-city-9-day-itinerary-4/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/mexico-city-9-day-itinerary-4/</guid>
        
        <category>Mexico City</category>
        
        
        <category>Mexico</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>February Goals {2016}</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Before discussing my February goals, here’s how I did in January:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Code for 10-15 minutes. {FAIL}&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
When I had most of my Javascript modules of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.freecodecamp.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FreeCodeCamp&lt;/a&gt; to complete, it wasn’t difficult to work on this daily. Towards the end of the month, I switched to prepping for Bali by reviewing HTML/CSS. Unfortunately, it wasn’t consistent, and I slacked a bit towards the end of the month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/slightlydelightful/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1713/24414664469_625abecf31_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Instagram&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Draw daily. {SUCCESS}&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
For 31 days, I participated in Lisa Congdon’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.creativebug.com/classseries/single/daily-drawing-challenge&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;31 Things to Draw daily challenge&lt;/a&gt; on Creative Bug. Check out the results on &lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/slightlydelightful/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get 600+ Misfit points. {SUCCESS}&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Ironically, I lost my Misfit tracker yesterday, so I won’t be tracking my activity this month. In January, I made efforts to be more active, and it worked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bed by midnight. {SUCCESS}&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Some days I would be in bed even before 11. Other days, I’d run into the room at 11:57. Regardless of the time, I was in the bed by midnight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No buying booze when out and about. {SUCCESS}&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This was actually not difficult at all and an easy way to save money. Even though I am not setting it as an official goal for February &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; there’s a bottomless brunch on the horizon, I’m going to try to keep this to a minimum and work through some of the beer and wine we have at home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1556/24155411543_fd264162bc_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Looking up, then down during a revisit to &lt;a href=&quot;http://superduperfantastic.com/big-red/3512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Armstrong Redwoods State Natural Reserve&lt;/a&gt; in January&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;february-goals&quot;&gt;February Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wake up by 7am.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The snooze button and I are BFFs, but hopefully not for much longer! This is on the flip side of the bedtime goal. Now that I’m more accustomed to hitting the hay by midnight, I should be able to get up when my alarm rings. I didn’t even pick a more ambitious time because I want to ease into this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily 3 praises.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In her &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ly_GlXOTA-A&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;keynote&lt;/a&gt; {link to video} at the 2015 Grace Hopper Celebration of Women in Computing, Sheryl Sandberg talks about the importance of reflection, especially reflection upon one’s own accomplishments regardless of the size. She challenged attendees to spend some time each day thinking about the three things they did well that day, so I am doing that in February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read 10-15 minutes daily.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
10 to 15 minutes is not very much of reading each day, but setting a minimum really does encourage me to do just a little. If the bar is set too high, it becomes intimidating and easier to just skip it altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work out at least 3x a week.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
It’s good to stay active, even if I no longer use a fitness tracker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m tracking these four goals with my &lt;a href=&quot;http://commit30.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Commit30&lt;/a&gt; planner. Even though I find that I’m not using the rest of the planner, I still use the monthly goal tracking page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are your goals for February?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 16:22:02 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/february-goals-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/february-goals-2016/</guid>
        
        <category>Goals</category>
        
        
        <category>Getting Personal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2015 Edition: Where Our Money Goes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the obsession I have over checking my spending and accounts, it’s a surprise I don’t talk about money more often. Where does our money go? Seeing the recent posts from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theinbetweenismine.com/2016/01/25/daily-life-spending-report-2015/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;San&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://lisasyarns.blogspot.com/2016/01/year-in-review-2015-spending.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lisa&lt;/a&gt; regarding their spending in 2015 has encouraged me to take a look and find out. Showing spending by percentages doesn’t quite give an accurate picture in terms of dollar amounts since it’s all relative. However, it shows what the priorities were in terms of where dollars went in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1720/24006704464_eb8a8b4dc7_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;where does our money go&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Home/Bills/Utilities&lt;/strong&gt; - This would be the largest area of spending. It includes mortgage, taxes, insurance, all house-related expenses, and bills. For the most part, these are fixed costs. That means if we do a good job of not spending so much in other areas this year, this percentage should actually go up relative to everything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food/Dining/Alcohol&lt;/strong&gt; - This is one of the categories that is a really high $ amount, but percentage-wise, it’s not really so much. A bulk of our food costs are related to eating out and also buying alcohol. Our groceries don’t usually cost very much, even when we’re buying organic and sustainable food. Even if we maintained the same percentage for this category, I’d like to see an internal shift from spending more eating in than out. Even though we didn’t set a &lt;a href=&quot;http://superduperfantastic.com/january-goals-2016/24209/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;specific goal in January&lt;/a&gt; for eating in more, we’re already doing it by ordering more produce from our various farm boxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shopping&lt;/strong&gt; - I’ve lumped gifts, clothing rentals and Ryan’s electronics and software purchases into this one, so it’s a larger percentage than I would like to be spending on THINGS. It also includes the various Kickstarters that I’ve backed because &lt;em&gt;Hey, that sounds like a brilliant idea!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt; - These are those unavoidable student loans that have to be paid off. The goal is to increase the percentage in this category because it means we’re paying off more of the loans!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Travel&lt;/strong&gt; - Some &lt;em&gt;might&lt;/em&gt; be a little surprised at how little we spend on travel. We stretch our dollars for our trips, flying on SW points if we can (like our trip to &lt;a href=&quot;http://superduperfantastic.com/tag/mexico-city/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mexico City&lt;/a&gt;), and staying in relatively inexpensive accommodations when possible. The numbers are a little skewed since we often buy our tickets a half year in advance, so last year’s trip to Belgium was paid for in 2014. The 2015 number does include my upcoming Bali trip, so it balances out in the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pets&lt;/strong&gt; - Having furry members of your family is not a large expense. The largest chunk of the costs in this category is pet insurance. After that, anytime we leave town and don’t bring Fresca along, it’s doggie daycare expenses. We could almost lump the doggie daycare expenses into our Travel category.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having the visual of the pie chart really does help put all of our spending in perspective. There were categories that I was certain I was spending more on, but it turned out that I was wrong. If you’ve tracked your spending for the year, what are some areas of spending that surprised you?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 16:20:45 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/2015-edition-where-does-our-money-go/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/2015-edition-where-does-our-money-go/</guid>
        
        <category>Goals</category>
        
        <category>Spending</category>
        
        
        <category>Money Matters</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Visiting the San Francisco Zoo</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ryan and I kicked off the new year with a visit to the San Francisco Zoo. The 100 acres in the southwestern corner of the city is home to over 1,000 exotic, endangered and rescued animals representing more than 250 species. I bought a membership last year, thinking we would visit a few times during the year. It expires at the end of the month, and I’ve only gone once in the year.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1554/23493946053_b92e7cb4b9_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Giraffes&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Giraffes are a favorite, even when they make faces like these…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1470/23752891479_97c668371c_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Llama&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;This little guy was making a similar face at me through the fence.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5674/24094650306_7a066899ab_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Lemur&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Go home, lemur. You’re drunk!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5764/23752854449_e68ee30125_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Flamingos&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
*Flamingos always look better than they smell. *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5649/23752889619_ee1a2d3b6c_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Anteater&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The most stylish at the zoo!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1482/23492435574_f26b5c7fcc_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Bobcat&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Fresca sleeps like this bobcat sometimes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In celebration of Penguin Awareness Day (January 20), here are some photos of the Magellanic penguins at the SF Zoo. It boasts the largest breeding colony of Magellanic penguins in captivity!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1588/24094593566_26d51d160e_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Magellanic Penguins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5694/23752878279_8a3b593736_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Magellanic Penguins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5819/24012581682_03b7148a2e_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;San Francisco Zoo - Magellanic Penguins&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;h3 id=&quot;visit-the-san-francisco-zoo&quot;&gt;Visit the San Francisco Zoo&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Sloat Blvd. at the Great Highway&lt;br /&gt;
San Francisco, CA. 94132&lt;br /&gt;
415.753.7080&lt;br /&gt;
More info: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sfzoo.org/&quot; title=&quot;San Francisco Zoo&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 13:51:47 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/san-francisco-zoo/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/san-francisco-zoo/</guid>
        
        <category>The Sunset</category>
        
        <category>zoo</category>
        
        
        <category>San Francisco</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>January Goals {2016}</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy 2016! This year, in place of “Currently” posts, I have “Goals” posts. I know we’re already almost in the middle of the month, but here are my goals for January:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Code for 10-15 minutes.&lt;/strong&gt;
The trip to Bali for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.instituteofcode.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Institute of Code&lt;/a&gt; is coming up next month, and I don’t feel ready for it at all. I don’t have a trip sponsor yet, and my requests to see prior session portfolios have been unanswered. In an effort to get my brain in coding mode, I am committing to completing &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.freecodecamp.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FreeCodeCamp&lt;/a&gt; modules at least six of the seven days of the week in January.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/2/1720/24222680812_073319b1e2_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;January Goals - 31 Things to Draw&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Draw daily.&lt;/strong&gt;
Right before the new year, I learned of Lisa Congdon’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.creativebug.com/classseries/single/daily-drawing-challenge&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;31 Things to Draw daily challenge&lt;/a&gt; on Creative Bug. Some of the things we’ve tackled in the first week and half: roses, cats, brooms, leaves, trees, birds. I’m posting them on &lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/slightlydelightful/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get 600+ Misfit points.&lt;/strong&gt;
Towards the end of 2015, I started using the Misfit fitness tracker. 600 points represents a life of low activity. I’ve been reaching my goal by playing Just Dance 2015 since I spend most of my day at a desk in front of a computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bed by midnight.&lt;/strong&gt;
It’s pretty self-explanatory. I’d love to get in bed by midnight. I’ve always been a night owl, but I’d like to make my mornings more productive, so the first step is getting to bed earlier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been tracking these four goals with my &lt;a href=&quot;http://commit30.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Commit30&lt;/a&gt; planner. There’s an additional goal/limitation I’ve placed on both Ryan and myself:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No buying booze when out and about.&lt;/strong&gt;
Saving money is high up there on my list for 2016. One of the areas I found that we spend quite a bit on is alcohol. It adds up, especially if we are grabbing dinner or drinks with friends. This month, when we’re out and about, we are sticking to only paying for non-alcoholic beverages. We also have plenty of beer and wine at home that we can work on instead.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 12:05:17 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/january-goals-2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/january-goals-2016/</guid>
        
        <category>Goals</category>
        
        
        <category>Getting Personal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mexico City in 9 Days (Part III)</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-four-in-mexico-city---centro-historico-with-journeys-beyond-the-surface&quot;&gt;DAY FOUR in Mexico City - Centro Historico with Journeys Beyond the Surface&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up to an email from Mojdeh of &lt;a href=&quot;http://travelmexicocity.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Journeys Beyond the Surface&lt;/a&gt;. Our tour guide fell ill, and our full day tour was cancelled. Thankfully, she gave us two other options - a full refund of the deposit &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; crashing a tour that someone else had with another guide for the same area for half a day or no tour at all. The choice seemed pretty obvious, so we crashed someone else’s tour!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We quickly hopped into an Uber to Centro Historico to catch up to our guide and new tour buddy. While I normally don’t take tours, I’m a huge proponent for taking one or two in Mexico City. You really learn so much about the history and context of all that you’re seeing. Spots visited on the tour: Metropolitan Cathedral, Palacio Nacional (Diego Rivera murals), Palacio de Bellas Artes, Palacio Postal, Plaza Manuel Tolsa, Sanborns de los Azulejos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5643/23536547660_f2ddc8eb0d_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Centro Historico&quot; title=&quot;Mexico City - Centro Historico&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately since we had an abrupt start to our morning, we didn’t get the chance to grab breakfast. Our stomachs were grumbling the entire time. When the Centro Historico portion of the tour wrapped, we went on our way to find food!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mercado de San Juan was walking distance away, so we headed over there. Unfortunately, we made the mistake of not sitting down for meat and cheeses, which the market is well-known for. Instead we picked a stand where there appeared to be a set menu. The man behind the counter asked if we wanted soup, so we took the soup and ate it. He then offered us rice, except it was just rice. It didn’t appear to come with anything, and we were not sure how to get a plate like the other people sitting at the same stand. So much confusion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since our full day tour became a half day tour, &lt;a href=&quot;http://travelmexicocity.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mojdeh&lt;/a&gt; gave us a list of recommendations on what else to check out in the area, like nearby graffiti art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5625/23806382116_a770f22a37_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Graffiti Art&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were intermittent rain showers, so we stopped in at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yelp.com/biz/al-andar-m%C3%A9xico-3&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Al Andar&lt;/a&gt; for drinks and a snack while the rain passes. The spot is known for mezcal, but we only tried some local beers. Once the rain let up a bit, we headed back to our Airbnb before dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on our Airbnb host’s recommendations, we decided to have sushi for dinner at &lt;a href=&quot;http://toritori.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tori Tori&lt;/a&gt; - Temistocles #61 in Polanco. The restaurant is uniquely designed and decorated, so it was neat to check it out. The food was delicious once we figured out how to order at the sushi counter. We were seated at the counter but were never handed a menu. When we finally got the sushi chef’s attention, he handed us a giant wooden board with the menu printed on it. So weird! At least the food was good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/1/739/23724247352_69613eeba1_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Tori Tori&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Tori Tori&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way back to the Airbnb, we stopped in at Helados Santa Clara for dessert. Thankfully that was a pretty straightforward ordering process, since the rest of the day had been full of confusing dining in Mexico City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-five-in-mexico-city---museums--graffiti-art&quot;&gt;DAY FIVE in Mexico City - Museums / Graffiti Art&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our most Instagram-genic photo came from breakfast on day five. We biked on over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://catamundi.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Catamundi&lt;/a&gt; and sat outside since the weather was gorgeous. I ended up ordering the most beautiful avocado toast. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/9u2F6mOBmZ/?taken-by=superduperfantastic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;No exaggeration&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After breakfast, we made our way over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://mna.inah.gob.mx/index.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Nacional de Antropologia&lt;/a&gt;. It was one of the most recommended museums, so we had to check it out. We were glad to have taken tours earlier on in the trip to make sense of what we were saying. There isn’t a whole lot of signage on the exhibits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our hunger and an Ecobici brought us to &lt;a href=&quot;http://mercadoroma.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mercado Roma&lt;/a&gt;, a really neat food/drink space, much more modern than any of the other markets we’d come across in Mexico City. After grabbing pressed juice upstairs, we sat and people watched. We also ordered some &lt;em&gt;tlacoyos&lt;/em&gt; at one of the stands since we had learned what they were on our &lt;a href=&quot;http://eatmexico.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eat Mexico&lt;/a&gt; tour earlier on in the trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/1/582/23509525496_3901059689_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Mercado Roma&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After our quick break at Mercado Roma, we walked over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://museodeljuguete.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo del Juguete Antiguo Mexico&lt;/a&gt; (MUJAM), even though biking would have been much faster. What an amazing space that was! When we first got there, we didn’t really have any idea where we were going, so we wandered around the property taking photos of some of the graffiti art. There was an entrance into a store downstairs, so we went in there, and finally someone inside told us that the museum entrance was actually up a dark stairway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We went up the dark stairway and rang the doorbell. It’s unassuming at first, but then we ended up spending the next few hours among old toys and wonderful graffiti art spread across many floors. We were lucky enough to meet the man/collector behind it all, Roberto Shimizu and learn about how and why he started collecting. We took so many photos here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/1/678/23207376123_7e22a604f1_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - MUJAM&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Museo del Juguete Antiguo Mexico aka MUJAM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We remembered a tip from Mojdeh about asking to see the rooftop. Definite pro tip there! The rooftop is &lt;em&gt;covered&lt;/em&gt;, and by the time we got up there, it was about sunset, so the views were also fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5806/23466253429_1345bd6fe0_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - MUJAM&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Rooftop of Museo del Juguete Antiguo Mexico aka MUJAM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For dinner, we decided to venture over to Little Koreatown in Mexico City. We recalled seeing some Korean restaurants during some of our Uber rides around the city. We ate dinner at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/pages/Mapo-Gal-Bi/172045342930531?rf=436111446446597&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ma Po Gal Bi&lt;/a&gt;, gorging ourselves on delicious Korean food and drinking way too much soju.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;h3 id=&quot;mexico-city---real-talk&quot;&gt;Mexico City - Real Talk&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;If you are riding &lt;a href=&quot;www.ecobici.df.gob.mx/en&quot;&gt;Ecobicis&lt;/a&gt;, use the app to find parking because people use these bikes to commute and some racks are more full than others. 
-Eat at &lt;a href=&quot;http://catamundi.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Catamundi&lt;/a&gt; or pick something up for later. The market inside looks amazing!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://mercadoroma.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mercado Roma&lt;/a&gt;, even for a snack or a juice. It’s a beautiful spot.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;MUJAM came recommended by &lt;a href=&quot;http://travelmexicocity.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Journeys Beyond the Surface&lt;/a&gt;, again for graffiti art. The toys, graffiti art, and meeting the owner were the highlight of our trip. Go see it if you have a few hours to spare. Ask to see the rooftop!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://mna.inah.gob.mx/index.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Nacional de Antropologia&lt;/a&gt; is the most visited museum in Mexico and recommended by most of our friends who have been to Mexico City. The tours we did earlier in our trip were incredibly helpful in giving a context to what we were seeing in the exhibits.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;More time can be dedicated to the museums in Centro Historico. It’s on our list for the next time!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 14:09:58 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/mexico-city-in-9-days-itinerary-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/mexico-city-in-9-days-itinerary-3/</guid>
        
        <category>Mexico City</category>
        
        
        <category>Mexico</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mexico City in 9 Days (Part II)</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5801/23135084203_c60e30957b_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-two-in-mexico-city---journeys-beyond-the-surface-full-day-tour-teotihuacan--basilica-de-nuestra-seora-de-guadalupe&quot;&gt;Day Two in Mexico City - Journeys Beyond the Surface Full Day Tour (Teotihuacan / Basilica de Nuestra Señora de Guadalupe)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up bright and early to meet our guide from &lt;a href=&quot;http://travelmexicocity.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Journeys Beyond the Surface&lt;/a&gt; for an exciting eight hours of sightseeing. Our first stop was the Plaza de las Tres Culturas in Tlatelolco, an archaeological excavation site in Mexico City. From there, our guide drove us up to the Pyramids of Teotihuacan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon arrival at Teotihuacan, I bought a hat, even though we bought sunscreen the night before. We spend some time learning, climbing, and picture taking. In the Plaza of the Moon, we clapped our hands to hear the echo and check out the acoustics of the space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5724/23736333806_a0db20a381_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Teotihuacan&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few hours later, it was time for lunch. We got a chance to admire the view of the pyramids from our restaurant (Mayahuel Restaurant) and to try &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pulque&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;pulque&lt;/a&gt; for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a little traffic on the way back to Mexico City, but that was more time for napping in the car. We decided that the next part of our tour would be Basilica de Nuestra Señora de Guadalupe, one of the most important pilgrimage sites in Catholicism. We walked the grounds, admired the cityscape (without the haze) and viewed the “original cloak” of Juan Diego with the image of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Our_Lady_of_Guadalupe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Our Lady of Guadalupe&lt;/a&gt; on a set of moving walkways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5808/23348897852_c5f12d319c_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The eight hours flew by. Our guide offered to drop us off at Panteón Civil de Dolores for another try at checking out the Dia de los Muertos festivities. Round 2 at the cemetery - this time, a success! We spent an hour or so wandering around and observing the festivities and decorated gravestones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For dinner, we made reservations online for &lt;a href=&quot;http://azul.rest/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Azul Condesa&lt;/a&gt;, which was a recommendation from our Airbnb hosts. After dinner, we walked over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://limantour.tv/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Licoreria Limantour&lt;/a&gt; (recommended by our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.eatmexico.com/&quot;&gt;Eat Mexico&lt;/a&gt; guide) in Roma Norte for drinks. It also happened to be #20 on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.worlds50bestbars.com/fifty-best-bars-list/Licoreria-Limantour.php?pid=ranking-2015-1-50&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;World’s 50 Best Bars of 2015&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/1/682/23429685886_10db084dcd_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Licoreria Limontour&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Lassi Orwell and Jamaica Mezcal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-three-in-mexico-city---museo-frida-kahlo--coyoacan--lucha-libre&quot;&gt;Day Three in Mexico City - Museo Frida Kahlo / Coyoacan / Lucha Libre&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before heading down to Coyoacan, we rode Ecobicis to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rosetta.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Panaderia Rosetta&lt;/a&gt; in Roma Norte. We definitely had to stop ourselves from ordering &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the baked goods. They were SO fantastic that we seriously considered returning for breakfast another day, but there were too many places to try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5624/23667520692_3d56848f81_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Panaderia Rosetta&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;I had bags under my eyes, but I was clearly pleased with the baked goodies from Panaderia Rosetta!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once fueled up, it was time for Coyoacan for &lt;a href=&quot;http://museofridakahlo.org.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Frida Kahlo&lt;/a&gt;. Since we didn’t reserve tickets online ahead of time, there was a small line, but it wasn’t anything too crazy. For permission to take photos inside Casa Azul, we bought a photo pass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5763/23428607622_bd389e41fb_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Casa Azul&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Altar at Casa Azul&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Casa Azul, we walked to Mercado de Coyoacan. At the first tostada stand we saw (Tostadas La Chaparrita), we sat down and started ordering from the platters of ceviche sitting out. Probably not the best idea to just sit down without scoping it out more thoroughly first, but we were hungry. It didn’t end up being a bad decision for the belly! Once satisfied, we wandered around the market and then out to the main square of Coyoacan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://museoculturaspopulares.gob.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Nacional de Culturas Populares&lt;/a&gt; was a pretty neat stop where we learned about &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/La_Familia_Burr%C3%B3n&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;La Familia Burron&lt;/a&gt;. Their Dia de los Muertos displays were still on exhibit, even though the related programs ended the day before, so there were some good photo opps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5668/23436024069_7209a76d6f_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Museo Nacional de Culturas Populares&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we were thinking of going to a Lucha Libre match, we checked online for the experience someone at our Airbnb hosts’ birthday BBQ a few days ago had recommended. The one he mentioned was a hop-on hop-off bus that leaves the Cathedral and included front row seats. The only hop-on hop-off bus affiliate we found (&lt;a href=&quot;http://turibus.com.mx/index.php?s=RutasTematicas&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Turi*Luchas&lt;/a&gt;) left from Reforma 222, a shopping mall on Paseo de la Reforma. We didn’t end up with a tour sitting in the front row, which might have been for the better. There was a lot of action on the ground!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/1/632/23435812899_9559fecaf9_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - TuriLuchas&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;h3 id=&quot;mexico-city---real-talk&quot;&gt;Mexico City - Real Talk&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Monday is a great day to visit Teotihuacan. Many museums are closed on Mondays, but Teotihuacan is not.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Make reservations for &lt;a href=&quot;http://museofridakahlo.org.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Museo Frida Kahlo&lt;/a&gt; if you know the specific time you want to visit. Otherwise, visit earlier in the day on a weekday.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Private tours with &lt;a href=&quot;http://travelmexicocity.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Journeys Beyond the Surface&lt;/a&gt; are a great way to see Mexico City. Your itinerary is created based on what you’re interested in. They’ll also provide suggestions for other days of your visit to Mexico City.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Eat the pastries at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rosetta.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Panaderia Rosetta&lt;/a&gt;. There have also been great reviews of the affiliated restaurant. It’s on my list for the next time I find myself in Mexico City.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Drink at &lt;a href=&quot;http://limantour.tv/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Licoreria Limantour&lt;/a&gt;. There’s another location in Polanco, but the one in Roma Norte is the one on the top bars list.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 23:50:03 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/mexico-city-9-days-itinerary-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/mexico-city-9-days-itinerary-2/</guid>
        
        <category>Mexico City</category>
        
        
        <category>Mexico</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mexico City in 9 Days (Part I)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mexico City was amazing. So much good food, sights to see, things to do. I don’t usually post itineraries or recaps in detail, but I need to get back in the blogging game. It may also be useful for those of you considering a trip to Mexico City. It’s a pretty quick flight from the states and a relatively inexpensive trip to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://superduperfantastic.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/Mexico-in-9-Days.png&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico in 9 Days&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;arrival-in-mexico-city---our-first-meals&quot;&gt;Arrival in Mexico City - Our First Meals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arrived at the airport and took an Uber to your Airbnb where we quickly dropped our bags off in our room and were whisked away by our hosts for a quick bite to eat. Delicious Marlin tacos at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/ElPescaditoCondesaDf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;El Pescadito Condesa DF&lt;/a&gt; were our first meal in Mexico City! Pro tip: Instead of standing in the long line to be seated inside at a table, order at the register for take out and pick up your food next door and enjoy on the bench right outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5723/23375003281_9e31b3f4c7_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - El Pescadito Condesa&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rest of the afternoon, we tried finding a working ATM and acquiring SIM cards for our phones. Unfortunately, we were met with no success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the evening, our hosts helped us with acquiring SIM cards, but we couldn’t quite figure out the ATM card situation. Thankfully our credit card worked because we had zero cash on us, not even a peso when the cute little kids all decked out in their Halloween costumes came trick or treating. They don’t trick or treat for candy (which I also had none of), so all I could do was turn them away when they approached us on the street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With our working phones, we made reservations for a fancy restaurant that we happened to walk by in Polanco. It was recommended to us by the community manager of Yelp Mexico City. We showed up to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.biko.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Biko&lt;/a&gt; in our street clothes, and while we felt awkward for the first five minutes, we soon ordered the tasting menu and shared a wine pairing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c1.staticflickr.com/1/577/23030067343_406d36fc5f_b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Biko&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a really big meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-one-in-mexico-city---eat-mexico--mercado-jamaica--birthday-bbq&quot;&gt;Day ONE in Mexico City - Eat Mexico / Mercado Jamaica / Birthday BBQ&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our first real day in Mexico City. Time to take advantage of all it has to offer! Ride Ecobicis to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://eatmexico.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eat Mexico&lt;/a&gt; tour you signed up for (Comidas &amp;amp; Calaveritas at Mercado Jamaica). Show up late because you didn’t realize how long it would take to get there. Good thing you got SIM cards the night before, so you can text your guide on your way to the meeting point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your tour starts, and once you arrive at Mercado Jamaica, your face stuffing begins. Tlacoyos with huitlacoche (aka corn fungus), tamales, champurrado/atole, quesadillas with squash blossoms, huaraches… All the while, you learn about preparations for Dia de los Muertos. The flowers, altars, paper cut-outs and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5802/23430232582_a413969592.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Mercado Jamaica&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5658/23374950341_8875294f8f.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Mercado Jamaica&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have so much food and fun, and hop on the subway back to your Airbnb once it’s all over and done!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;AFTERNOON:&lt;/u&gt; Hang out with your Airbnb hosts and their friends because they’re having a birthday BBQ! Eat delicious foods, drink beer, and chit chat with the locals. Take a blurry selfie. It’ll be the only photo you have with one of your amazing Airbnb hosts!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5647/23631292646_e13dc1eb96.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Birthday BBQ&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://c2.staticflickr.com/6/5715/23170407199_50d1049a1f_n.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mexico City - Panteon Civil de Dolores&quot; /&gt;&lt;u&gt;EVENING:&lt;/u&gt; Take a break from the party to check out some Dia de los Muertos festivities! Grab an Uber for &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pante%C3%B3n_de_Dolores&quot;&gt;Panteón Civil de Dolores&lt;/a&gt;, the largest cemetery in Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After telling your Uber that you’re absolutely sure you want to be dropped off there, you wander the perimeter of the cemetery. There’s nobody in sight, and it’s super dark out. You come to the conclusion that it is CLOSED. You got here too late. Festivities ended by 9pm! Time to head back to the Airbnb. Luckily, the party is still bumping!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now to figure out the ATM situation. Finally give in and call your bank via Skype because there’s no way every single ATM in Mexico City does not work with your card. Verify your identity and that you’ve walked up to over a handful ATMs, trying to withdraw varying amounts in order to test your card. Once cleared, test the card at an ATM because you need cash to pay your tour guide the next day. It FINALLY works! &lt;em&gt;phew&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buy beer for the party, using cash because their card reader is broken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;h3 id=&quot;mexico-city---real-talk&quot;&gt;Mexico City - REAL TALK&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Use Uber to get around. If you have access to an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecobici.df.gob.mx/en&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ecobici&lt;/a&gt;, the bikes are great for quick trips.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Make sure to notify your banks/credit cards early.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;For SIM cards, get a smaller card first. Add minutes/data online or at a convenient store later. We used Telcel.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Book a food/market tour with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.eatmexico.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eat Mexico&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a bit more expensive, but worth it!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Panteón Civil de Dolores closes by 9pm. Get there in the early evening for Dia de Muertos festivities!&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Eat at: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/ElPescaditoCondesaDf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;El Pescadito Condesa DF&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.biko.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Biko&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 10:23:16 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/mexico-city-9-day-itinerary-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://superduperfantastic.com/blog/mexico-city-9-day-itinerary-1/</guid>
        
        <category>Mexico City</category>
        
        
        <category>Mexico</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
